{
    "id": "40ec602a0d4b49578299e440d65aeaa4",
    "title": "Gap Filling Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "At least six people have ……………….. in the explosion.",
            "description": "Died is the past tense of die.",
            "answers": [
                "dies",
                "died",
                "dead"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d891c8249685466cbce41f257b1edb1e"
        },
        {
            "question": "By the time they found him, he was already ……………………….",
            "description": "Dead is an adjective. Died is a verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "died",
                "dead"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "efd264ce171a478cb143363d9b0ad6c9"
        },
        {
            "question": "She …………………… in the morning.",
            "description": "The simple past is used when we say when something happened.",
            "answers": [
                "left",
                "has left",
                "leaved"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6b0d6d1650d94a06a2a7eef821bb1bd0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Let’s ………………………. your plans.",
            "description": "Discuss is one of those verbs that are not followed by a preposition.",
            "answers": [
                "discuss",
                "discuss about",
                "discuss over"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ba1d4dc9ea2a4292ab45b2a7bfb2cba7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………… him a visit the other day.",
            "description": "Paid is the past tense of pay.",
            "answers": [
                "payed",
                "paid",
                "have paid"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "17594711db1f4a5a8d58533c0a74f6f7"
        },
        {
            "question": "You haven’t …………………….. for your drinks.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "payed",
                "paid",
                "pay"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "50ab804b4b994a0c9a377cb61e288c32"
        },
        {
            "question": "She …………………….. her dress and went out.",
            "description": "To put on dress is to wear it. ",
            "answers": [
                "took on",
                "put on",
                "brought on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ef44f47881a6431ca7e690eb4be7a7c7"
        },
        {
            "question": "What a brilliant idea ……………………..!",
            "description": "The inverted word order is used in exclamations.",
            "answers": [
                "is it",
                "it is",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fa9d009f1c0242588708459438d17948"
        },
        {
            "question": "Tell me why ………………………. to leave now.",
            "description": "The inverted word order is used in indirect questions. ",
            "answers": [
                "want you",
                "do you want",
                "you want"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5b860d0a61de4813b9fcfbef6ae07849"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ……………………… listen to your doctor.",
            "description": "Had better is used to give strong advice or warnings.",
            "answers": [
                "have better",
                "had better",
                "had to better"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4c1afb4e13964501923759893a8db072"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you started early, you …………………….. miss the bus.",
            "description": "In the second conditional, we use a simple past tense in the if-clause and would + first form of the verb in the main clause.",
            "answers": [
                "won't",
                "wouldn't",
                "hadn't"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "673ee71d2eb84ca493a71e63a322670a"
        },
        {
            "question": "A cousin of ………………….. is an actor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "me",
                "my",
                "mine"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9701ef849a7c48c89efe72d8a84ae4eb"
        }
    ]
}